LSU football held their annual pro day
Monday 17 draft eligible players out of
LSU participated as they are making
their pact to the [music] draft
presented by Cox. Saints executives,
coaches, and scouts were in attendance
along with everyone else in the NFL to
watch these players compete. They were
able to showcase their skills and
drills, measurements, and on field
workouts. A lot of players who didn't
participate in the combine [music] were
participants here today. We got to see
cornerback Mansour Delane run the 40 for
the first time. He did it in 4 3 [music]
5 time. So, really good performance from
him. He is slated to go in the first
round, could [music] be a top 10 pick.
The Saints picking at number eight are
definitely on the board for potentially
drafting [music] him. Along with Delane,
quarterback Garrett Nussmeier was able
to throw to his receivers, fellow LSU
players. Um, it was cool just to to get
to play with those guys one last time,
you know, kind of get to do our thing,
have a little fun with it, but it was
awesome. Saints offensive coordinator
Doug Nussmeier, the father of Garrett,
[music] was also in attendance to watch
his son and scout the rest of the pro
day. I think they actually had a pretty
good workout, you know what I mean? I
think they uh the whole group, the guys
ran well, caught well. I thought it was
a really clean workout, uh high level
execution on some stuff from all of
them. LSU linebacker [music] Harold
Perkins also competed on the on field
portion. He ran a 4 4 40, so has an
official time there. He is somebody that
is slated to go in the top rounds in the
NFL draft coming up very soon. So, stick
with us on New Orleans Saints.com. We
will continue to follow pro days and
countdown to the NFL draft.